<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Children on Dusty Turner</title>
    <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/categories/children/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Children on Dusty Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.dustysturner.com/categories/children/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Losing UNO to a 5 Year Old: An Exercise In Probability</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/losing-uno-to-a-5-year-old-an-exercise-in-probability/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/losing-uno-to-a-5-year-old-an-exercise-in-probability/</guid>
      <description>Background&#xD;One of my son’s favorite games he received for Christmas this year is UNO Attack. If you are not familiar with the rules, you can get up to speed here. In short, the rules are no different than usual UNO except when you cannot play, instead of taking a card, you press a button on an UNO card shooting contraption. Most of the time you get no cards, but some of the time it will “attack” with 1 or more cards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goal: Read 1000 (Children&#39;s) Books in 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-12-27-analysis-of-my-children-s-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-12-27-analysis-of-my-children-s-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>Introduction&#xD;Over Christmas 2017, my wife, Jill, resolved that our family (to include babysitters) would read our children over 1000 new books in 2018. More specifically, 29 December 2017 - 28 December 2018.&#xA;A goal like this takes dedication, love, and of course, a Data Science-y approach.&#xA;Special thanks to Ally, Zia, and Bookbuddy for help in accomplishing this goal!&#xA;Also, special thanks to drob and juliasilge who privde the tidytext package and the entire R open-source community I rely on to do this analysis.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
