<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>datascience on Dusty Turner</title>
    <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/tags/datascience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in datascience on Dusty Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.dustysturner.com/tags/datascience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Farewell Ode To My Old Grey Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/a-farewell-ode-to-my-old-grey-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/a-farewell-ode-to-my-old-grey-truck/</guid>
      <description>A Tribute!&#xD;Since the dawn of time, people have been developing human-like attachments to their transportation. I imagine Moses naming his chariot, Noah his ark, and maybe even Jesus naming his borrowed donkey.&#xA;Well, maybe I’m taking too much historical license, but man’s affinity for their transportation remains.&#xA;At the age of 21, my dad and I split the cost of a 2005 Ford F150. The odometer read ~24,000 miles and it set us back ~$20,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Football 2019 Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/fantasy-football-2019-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/fantasy-football-2019-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Goal of this Analysis&#xD;One of my superpowers is being a bad fantasy football manager. My motivation for this analysis is to show how I’m not actually that bad - but rather unlucky. To show this, I created this post.&#xA;Below I summarize how I got the data, the information I can glean from the data, share the link to this analysis for my league, and share the code so you can do it to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blog Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/blog-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/blog-introduction/</guid>
      <description>As my experience with statistics, computer science, and the all encompasing term, data science, increases, I have decided that it is time to share some of my projects.&#xA;Creating this blog serves several purposes.&#xA;It archives some projects I’ve created.&#xD;It makes my work public so I can receive (hopefully) constructive feedback to improve my tools/analysis.&#xA;It helps me share what I’ve learned with the community that has been so helpful to me.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
