<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dusty Turner</title>
    <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dusty Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.dustysturner.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Presentations</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/presentations/</guid>
      <description>More to follow as I rebuild my blog
Joint Statistical Meetings: 2018 Center for Data Analysis and Statistics 2018 NY R Conference Military Operations Research Symposium 2017 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Family I am a husband to Jill and a dad to Cal and Reese. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent 10 years in the Army and currently teach at The United States Military Academy at West Point, NY.
Motivation While I teach statistics, Data Science has become my hobby. I hope to improve my skills in statistics, machine learning, and computer science to make improvments within the Army and to the world at large.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/community/</guid>
      <description>What follows is a growing collection of examples of why I am grateful to be a part of this community.
 I met @jaredlander at the 2017 MIT Sloan Sports Analytics Conference. He gave a phenomenal talk (except for the focus on the NY Giants), and he was gracious in his conversation afterwards. We&amp;rsquo;ve had several interactions in the ensuing months &amp;ndash; What a great mentor!
Thank you @DTDusty for my new army frisbee!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit and R Part 1: Accessing Data with the Fitbit API</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2022-06-17-fitbit-api-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2022-06-17-fitbit-api-1/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionIn part 1 of this series, I will demonstrate how to interact with the Fitbit API in R.
Huge credit to Matt Kaye for creating the fitbitr package that provides an interface between R and the Fitbit API. If you are familiar with R and you have a Fitbit, you should have success following what I have laid out below.
Install the fitbitr packageFrom CRAN:
install.packages(&amp;quot;fitbitr&amp;quot;)Or the development version from github:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2021-12-01-advent-of-code-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2021-12-01-advent-of-code-2021/</guid>
      <description>Every year, the great team at Advent of Code lead by ericwastl develops an “Advent calendar of small programming puzzles for a variety of skill sets and skill levels that can be solved in any programming language you like.”
Well, I like R, so in this post I will provide my solutions to the puzzles each day. I plan on using this post to learn and teach and hopefully I am able to stay up-to-date!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Reboot</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2021-06-24-blog-reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2021-06-24-blog-reboot/</guid>
      <description>Friends - you may notice my blog if missing a few historical posts. The underlying open source software I&amp;rsquo;m using to build this blog undertook enough updates (for the better) that my patchwork site built on a house of cards came tumbling down.
I learned a lot in the process (which is the reason for even having a blog) and I&amp;rsquo;m reviving it. I&amp;rsquo;m removing some pages that I just can&amp;rsquo;t resussatate and consolodating some others (namly those about presentations).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Peloton API Part 2: A Peloton Data Tribute to my Wife</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/the-peloton-api-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/the-peloton-api-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Peloton RIn part 1 of my Peloton API post, I explored the pelotonR created by Ben Weiher’s. It’s a great package for accessing your Peloton data and I recommend it.
In part 2, I’ll explore a different pelotonR package from Laura Ellis. She provides a great tutorial to display the functionality. I recommend this one too!
ObjectivesThe objectives for this post are to…
Show how awesome my wife is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winning &#34;Pay The Rent&#34; on The Price Is Right</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/winning-pay-the-rent-on-the-price-is-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/winning-pay-the-rent-on-the-price-is-right/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in a previous blog post, my family and I have found different activities to do as all our other activities are on hold due to the COVID-19 lockdown.
In that post, I looked at first player’s strategy when spinning the big wheel prior to the showcase showdown.
In this post, I’ll explore the rarely won game, Pay the Rent
Pay The RentPay The RentPay The Rent is a challenging game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football 2020 Part 1: Accessing the API</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-api-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-api-2020/</guid>
      <description>Its that time of year!Its that time of year again. The time when we dust off the old ESPN fantasy football API R code and fix everything that broke in the last year.
Here’s what I hope to show over the next few posts.
How to access your ESPN public fantasy football league’s data.How to organize that data and create a few interesting displays.How to create a dashboard to supplement your league’s fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Peloton API Part 1: Accessing and Exploring</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/the-peloton-api-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/the-peloton-api-part-1/</guid>
      <description>In 2018, my wife and I were fortunate enough to find a deeply discounted Peloton on an online garage sale. Since then, she’s been going hard and I have been trying to keep up when the weather is bad or injuries keep me from running.
Jill Smiling After Her 600th Ride (and new record)!Over the last few months, a few works projects have taught me a lot about purrr, functional programming, collaborative projects, and APIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheel Spin Strategy On The Price Is Right</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/wheel-spin-strategy-on-the-price-is-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/wheel-spin-strategy-on-the-price-is-right/</guid>
      <description>MotivationLike many, COVID-19 completely altered our lives as the virus spread across the country and became a mainstay in our society. Though my family and I have been spared of tragedy, we’ve had to find ways to replace kid’s activities, work routines, and social interactions with other (hopefully) enriching activities… Like family games.
Ticket to Ride caused a lot of strife between my kids :)One thing that we’ve added to our new normal is watching “The Price is Right” after dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Farewell Ode To My Old Grey Truck</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/a-farewell-ode-to-my-old-grey-truck/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/a-farewell-ode-to-my-old-grey-truck/</guid>
      <description>A Tribute!Since the dawn of time, people have been developing human-like attachments to their transportation. I imagine Moses naming his chariot, Noah his ark, and maybe even Jesus naming his borrowed donkey.
Well, maybe I’m taking too much historical license, but man’s affinity for their transportation remains.
At the age of 21, my dad and I split the cost of a 2005 Ford F150.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Football 2019 Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/fantasy-football-2019-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/fantasy-football-2019-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Goal of this AnalysisOne of my superpowers is being a bad fantasy football manager. My motivation for this analysis is to show how I’m not actually that bad - but rather unlucky. To show this, I created this post.
Below I summarize how I got the data, the information I can glean from the data, share the link to this analysis for my league, and share the code so you can do it to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football V3 API for Private Leagues: An R Solution (Finally!)</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-an-r-solution-finally/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-an-r-solution-finally/</guid>
      <description>Accessing ESPN’s New V3 API for Private Leagues: How We Got HereThis marks post 3 of n of my 2019 ESPN Fantasy Football blog posts. In the last few months, ESPN upgraded their API from V2 to V3, breaking all of our previous work accessing and analysing the data from the API.
In my last two posts, I explored how to access data from ESPN’s V3 API for public leagues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football V3 API for Private Leagues: Python Through R</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-python-through-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-python-through-r/</guid>
      <description>Accessing ESPN Fantasy Football for Private LeaguesIn my previous post, I explained how to access the ESPN Fantasy Football’s new (V3) public API. But what if your league manager does not make the league public? Are you out of luck?
In this post I’ll explain how to pass ‘cookies’ to ESPN and access private league data.
To accomplish this, we’ll use…
PythonretriculatepurrrPython?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football V3 API for Public Leagues: An R Solution</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-an-r-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-an-r-solution/</guid>
      <description>ESPN’s New API (V3)In previous seasons, we’ve enjoyed relatively easy access to ESPN’s fantasy sports data. Sometime in the last few months, ESPN altered/upgraded their AP to V3.
As I’ve tried to replicate previous analysis, old methods accessing the V2 API no longer work.
Credit Where Credit Is DueQuick crash course on ESPN’s new #fantasyfootball API, #python focused — https://t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parallel Processing and Bootstrapping</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/parallel-processing-and-bootstrapping-for-diamonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/parallel-processing-and-bootstrapping-for-diamonds/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionOften times, I run simulations on my computer to help educate my students about different statistical topics. In doing this, I often end up running fairly “long” simulations that take up more time than what I’d like to use in the classrooms.
Complaining about this let me to Googling, which, as usual, let me to a solution. Posted below is an example of what I learned with an accompanying ShinyApp which helps me explain bootstrapping to my students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing The turnR Package</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/introducing-the-turnr-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/introducing-the-turnr-package/</guid>
      <description>InspirationAt the 2019 New York R Conference, Emily Robinson gave a great talk called “Everything You Wanted to Know About Making R Packages but Were Afraid to Ask” (Note: This link will be live once the video is published).
Emily Robinson is one of my ‘heros of R.’ I was honored to host her several years back a the United States Military Academy when she came to present her work on A/B Testing during her time at Esty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cadet Summer Tracker 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/cadet-summer-tracker-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/cadet-summer-tracker-2019/</guid>
      <description>It is our last summer at West Point! We will sure miss our cadets. To keep touch with everyone, I’ve created a ShinyApp (embedded below) that shows the location (and dates) of everyone over the summer training period.
If you’d rather view the app outside the blog, here is the link
----</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Losing UNO to a 5 Year Old: An Exercise In Probability</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/losing-uno-to-a-5-year-old-an-exercise-in-probability/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/losing-uno-to-a-5-year-old-an-exercise-in-probability/</guid>
      <description>BackgroundOne of my son’s favorite games he received for Christmas this year is UNO Attack. If you are not familiar with the rules, you can get up to speed here. In short, the rules are no different than usual UNO except when you cannot play, instead of taking a card, you press a button on an UNO card shooting contraption. Most of the time you get no cards, but some of the time it will “attack” with 1 or more cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 Mathlete Fantasy Football Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/mathlete-fantasy-football-analysis2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/mathlete-fantasy-football-analysis2018/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionIn my previous post, I worked through how to get your league information from the ESPN and YAHOO APIs.
The motivation for this project was to compare two leagues performances over the 2018 fantasy football season. As the ring leader of the West Point Department of Mathematical Sciences fantasy football league, we had 20 managers. This, of course, is too many for one league so we split the teams across two leagues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal: Read 1000 (Children&#39;s) Books in 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-12-27-analysis-of-my-children-s-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-12-27-analysis-of-my-children-s-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionOver Christmas 2017, my wife, Jill, resolved that our family (to include babysitters) would read our children over 1000 new books in 2018. More specifically, 29 December 2017 - 28 December 2018.
A goal like this takes dedication, love, and of course, a Data Science-y approach.
Special thanks to Ally, Zia, and Bookbuddy for help in accomplishing this goal!
Also, special thanks to drob and juliasilge who privde the tidytext package and the entire R open-source community I rely on to do this analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Dates in R</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/dates-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/dates-in-r/</guid>
      <description>A Little About Dates in RBefore we launch into any analysis that contains dates, we should know a few important nuggets about how R handles date-like objects.
There are 3 date/time classes are built in to R
- Date
- POSIXct
- POSIXlt
Base RFirst, base R can read a string of text and convert it to a date class. To help it read the date, you must tell R what date format your character string should expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking My Cadet&#39;s Summer Plans</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/tracking-my-cadets-summer-plans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/tracking-my-cadets-summer-plans/</guid>
      <description>Tracking my cadet’s summer plans with dplyr and ggplot. The interactive ShinyApp is below!% --% --% --% --% --% --% --% --% --% --</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018 NY R Conference Presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-ny-r-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-ny-r-conference/</guid>
      <description>Was honored to speak at this years 2018 New York R Conference hosted by Lander Analytics and Work-Bench. Jared Lander sure knows how to host a good party, I mean, conference.
My Slides are available, and you can contact me at dusty.s.turner@gmail.com
Here is the youtube link to the video:

Oh, and I got to go for a little run before the conference!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>This is my resume.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/blog-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/blog-introduction/</guid>
      <description>As my experience with statistics, computer science, and the all encompasing term, data science, increases, I have decided that it is time to share some of my projects.
Creating this blog serves several purposes.
It archives some projects I’ve created.It makes my work public so I can receive (hopefully) constructive feedback to improve my tools/analysis.
It helps me share what I’ve learned with the community that has been so helpful to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/links/</guid>
      <description>&amp;mdash; date: &amp;ldquo;2014-04-09&amp;rdquo; layout: links menu: main title: Links weight: 0 &amp;mdash;  Ritchie and his friends. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
