<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Dusty Turner</title>
    <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Dusty Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.dustysturner.com/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with GPU-Accelerated Machine Learning on AWS EC2 using R and TensorFlow</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2024-01-29-getting-started-with-gpu-accelerated-machine-learning-on-aws-ec2-using-r-and-tensorflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2024-01-29-getting-started-with-gpu-accelerated-machine-learning-on-aws-ec2-using-r-and-tensorflow/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionI’ve been looking for an all-in-one place to explain how to start from nothing to having a GPU-accelerated machine learning platform that runs RStudio Server with TensorFlow through reticulate.
In this post, I will explain how to…
Set up an EC2 instance in AWS with GPU capabilitiesInstall RStudio Server with the latest versions of RInstall the correct versions of Python with RecitulateInstall TensorFlow and Keras to run deep learning modelsSet up an EC2 instanceLog in to AWSFor a new account, select “Root User”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2021-12-01-advent-of-code-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2021-12-01-advent-of-code-2021/</guid>
      <description>Every year, the great team at Advent of Code lead by ericwastl develops an “Advent calendar of small programming puzzles for a variety of skill sets and skill levels that can be solved in any programming language you like.”
Well, I like R, so in this post I will provide my solutions to the puzzles each day. I plan on using this post to learn and teach and hopefully I am able to stay up-to-date!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winning &#34;Pay The Rent&#34; on The Price Is Right</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/winning-pay-the-rent-on-the-price-is-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/winning-pay-the-rent-on-the-price-is-right/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in a previous blog post, my family and I have found different activities to do as all our other activities are on hold due to the COVID-19 lockdown.
In that post, I looked at first player’s strategy when spinning the big wheel prior to the showcase showdown.
In this post, I’ll explore the rarely won game, Pay the Rent
Pay The RentPay The RentPay The Rent is a challenging game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football 2020 Part 1: Accessing the API</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-api-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-api-2020/</guid>
      <description>Its that time of year!Its that time of year again. The time when we dust off the old ESPN fantasy football API R code and fix everything that broke in the last year.
Here’s what I hope to show over the next few posts.
How to access your ESPN public fantasy football league’s data.How to organize that data and create a few interesting displays.How to create a dashboard to supplement your league’s fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal: Read 1000 (Children&#39;s) Books in 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-12-27-analysis-of-my-children-s-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-12-27-analysis-of-my-children-s-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionOver Christmas 2017, my wife, Jill, resolved that our family (to include babysitters) would read our children over 1000 new books in 2018. More specifically, 29 December 2017 - 28 December 2018.
A goal like this takes dedication, love, and of course, a Data Science-y approach.
Special thanks to Ally, Zia, and Bookbuddy for help in accomplishing this goal!
Also, special thanks to drob and juliasilge who privde the tidytext package and the entire R open-source community I rely on to do this analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/blog-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/blog-introduction/</guid>
      <description>As my experience with statistics, computer science, and the all encompasing term, data science, increases, I have decided that it is time to share some of my projects.
Creating this blog serves several purposes.
It archives some projects I’ve created.It makes my work public so I can receive (hopefully) constructive feedback to improve my tools/analysis.
It helps me share what I’ve learned with the community that has been so helpful to me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
