<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on Dusty Turner</title>
    <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on Dusty Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.dustysturner.com/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with GPU-Accelerated Machine Learning on AWS EC2 using R and TensorFlow</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2024-01-29-getting-started-with-gpu-accelerated-machine-learning-on-aws-ec2-using-r-and-tensorflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2024-01-29-getting-started-with-gpu-accelerated-machine-learning-on-aws-ec2-using-r-and-tensorflow/</guid>
      <description>Introduction&#xD;I’ve been looking for an all-in-one place to explain how to start from nothing to having a GPU-accelerated machine learning platform that runs RStudio Server with TensorFlow through reticulate.&#xA;In this post, I will explain how to…&#xA;Set up an EC2 instance in AWS with GPU capabilities&#xD;Install RStudio Server with the latest versions of R&#xD;Install the correct versions of Python with Recitulate&#xD;Install TensorFlow and Keras to run deep learning models&#xD;Set up an EC2 instance&#xD;Log in to AWS&#xD;For a new account, select “Root User”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football V3 API for Private Leagues: Python Through R</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-python-through-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-python-through-r/</guid>
      <description>Accessing ESPN Fantasy Football for Private Leagues&#xD;In my previous post, I explained how to access the ESPN Fantasy Football’s new (V3) public API. But what if your league manager does not make the league public? Are you out of luck?&#xA;In this post I’ll explain how to pass ‘cookies’ to ESPN and access private league data.&#xA;To accomplish this, we’ll use…&#xA;Python&#xD;retriculate&#xD;purrr&#xD;Python?!&#xD;Yes - Believe it or not, though I’m an avid R user, I believe in using the best tool for the job.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
