<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shiny on Dusty Turner</title>
    <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/categories/shiny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shiny on Dusty Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.dustysturner.com/categories/shiny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cadet Summer Tracker 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/cadet-summer-tracker-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/cadet-summer-tracker-2019/</guid>
      <description>It is our last summer at West Point! We will sure miss our cadets. To keep touch with everyone, I’ve created a ShinyApp (embedded below) that shows the location (and dates) of everyone over the summer training period.&#xA;If you’d rather view the app outside the blog, here is the link</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Losing UNO to a 5 Year Old: An Exercise In Probability</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/losing-uno-to-a-5-year-old-an-exercise-in-probability/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/losing-uno-to-a-5-year-old-an-exercise-in-probability/</guid>
      <description>Background&#xD;One of my son’s favorite games he received for Christmas this year is UNO Attack. If you are not familiar with the rules, you can get up to speed here. In short, the rules are no different than usual UNO except when you cannot play, instead of taking a card, you press a button on an UNO card shooting contraption. Most of the time you get no cards, but some of the time it will “attack” with 1 or more cards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 NY R Conference Presentation</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-ny-r-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/2018-ny-r-conference/</guid>
      <description>Was honored to speak at this years 2018 New York R Conference hosted by Lander Analytics and Work-Bench. Jared Lander sure knows how to host a good party, I mean, conference.&#xA;My Slides are available, and you can contact me at dusty.s.turner@gmail.com&#xA;Here is the youtube link to the video:&#xA;Oh, and I got to go for a little run before the conference!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
