<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ESPN API on Dusty Turner</title>
    <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/tags/espn-api/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ESPN API on Dusty Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.dustysturner.com/tags/espn-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Football 2019 Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/fantasy-football-2019-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/fantasy-football-2019-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The Goal of this Analysis&#xD;One of my superpowers is being a bad fantasy football manager. My motivation for this analysis is to show how I’m not actually that bad - but rather unlucky. To show this, I created this post.&#xA;Below I summarize how I got the data, the information I can glean from the data, share the link to this analysis for my league, and share the code so you can do it to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football V3 API for Private Leagues: An R Solution (Finally!)</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-an-r-solution-finally/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-an-r-solution-finally/</guid>
      <description>Accessing ESPN’s New V3 API for Private Leagues: How We Got Here&#xD;This marks post 3 of n of my 2019 ESPN Fantasy Football blog posts. In the last few months, ESPN upgraded their API from V2 to V3, breaking all of our previous work accessing and analysing the data from the API.&#xA;In my last two posts, I explored how to access data from ESPN’s V3 API for public leagues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football V3 API for Private Leagues: Python Through R</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-python-through-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-for-private-leagues-python-through-r/</guid>
      <description>Accessing ESPN Fantasy Football for Private Leagues&#xD;In my previous post, I explained how to access the ESPN Fantasy Football’s new (V3) public API. But what if your league manager does not make the league public? Are you out of luck?&#xA;In this post I’ll explain how to pass ‘cookies’ to ESPN and access private league data.&#xA;To accomplish this, we’ll use…&#xA;Python&#xD;retriculate&#xD;purrr&#xD;Python?!&#xD;Yes - Believe it or not, though I’m an avid R user, I believe in using the best tool for the job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN Fantasy Football V3 API for Public Leagues: An R Solution</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-an-r-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/espn-fantasy-football-v3-api-an-r-solution/</guid>
      <description>ESPN’s New API (V3)&#xD;In previous seasons, we’ve enjoyed relatively easy access to ESPN’s fantasy sports data. Sometime in the last few months, ESPN altered/upgraded their AP to V3.&#xA;As I’ve tried to replicate previous analysis, old methods accessing the V2 API no longer work.&#xA;Credit Where Credit Is Due&#xD;Quick crash course on ESPN’s new #fantasyfootball API, #python focused — https://t.co/bwPLJLDpmk pic.twitter.com/exi2NKLXV3&#xD;— Steven Morse (@thestevemo) August 1, 2019&#xD;I must also credit this reddit thread where one of the users shared the URL with end points that provide the all the available data requests for the API (as far as I can tell).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 Mathlete Fantasy Football Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/mathlete-fantasy-football-analysis2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.dustysturner.com/post/mathlete-fantasy-football-analysis2018/</guid>
      <description>Introduction&#xD;In my previous post, I worked through how to get your league information from the ESPN and YAHOO APIs.&#xA;The motivation for this project was to compare two leagues performances over the 2018 fantasy football season. As the ring leader of the West Point Department of Mathematical Sciences fantasy football league, we had 20 managers. This, of course, is too many for one league so we split the teams across two leagues.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
